<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Readings on Harrison Fritz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Readings on Harrison Fritz</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:07:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stuff I Read</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reading/stuff-i-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 20:51:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reading/stuff-i-read/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a non-exhaustive list of things(books, essays, posts, blogs, etc.) that I have read, partially or fully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;stuff-ive-read&#34;&gt;stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve read&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;james-by-percival-everett&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/173754979-james&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer nofollow&#34;&gt;James&lt;/a&gt; by Percival Everett&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rating-910&#34;&gt;rating: 9/10&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;thoughts&#34;&gt;Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lots of great perosnification and beautiful writing - &amp;ldquo;the wind became wild and stirred the fire&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The magic of this book is that the author actually pulls it off. What starts as a seemingly cheap gimmick - a retelling of Hucklberry Finn from a different viewpoint with a counterveiling perspective - actually works, raises some interesting issues, and creates a compelling character arch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The book is episodic and reads like a movie script. The ending is somewaht tarentinoesque and very satisfying, but feels  a bit rushed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The metametanarrative is the most impressive thing about this book. The narrative being the story of James chasing freedom, the metanarrative being the book&amp;rsquo;s social comentary on slavery and racism, and the metametanarrative being the book&amp;rsquo;s implicit commentary on how slavery and more generally black people are portrayed in other media (Huckleberry Finn). That is, without Huckleberry Finn, this book is still enjoyable, but not nearly as interesting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;selected-excerpts&#34;&gt;Selected Excerpts&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The wind became wild and stirred the fire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
